Guide to the Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
- Series III. Publications
  - Cornell Publications
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension- Ever Evolving, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - People and Their Communities in New York State, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Resolving Public Issues and Concerns through Policy Education, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Fit it all Together, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Program Development Model, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Staffing for the Future, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Cornell University College of Human Ecology: A Guide for Transfer, Special, and Mature Students, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Issue-Focused Programming in Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Community, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - The Cornell Cooperative Extension System, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension- Young Children: Priority One, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Cornell Extension, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Education for Living, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Report: Extension Programs for Limited-Resource Audiences in New York State, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Extension Administration in the 90's, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Cornell Extension, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Metropolitan Programming in New York State, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Research and Extension Accomplishments, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Resources for Legislation and Service to Constituents in the 1990's, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - Cornell Public Education Documents, 1993-2000 (Box 47, Folder 49A)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension goes "Beyond Rhetoric" to meet the national agenda for America's Children and Families, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - Cornell Extension, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 39)
    - Cornell Research and Extension in the News, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 40)
    - Relationship Marketing with Congressional members and State Legislators, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - Integrated Management for Flies in and around Dairy and Livestock Barns By Watson D Wes, 1994 (Box 53)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Program Catalyst, 1994-08-1997-02 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Framing the Future, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Turning Good Ideas into Great Programs, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Menu for Mealtimes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension: Helping You Put Knowledge to Work, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Protecting the Well-Being of 4-H Youth, 1996-10 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Parent-Adolescent Communication, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    - Pathway to the 21st Century: Strategic Directions for the Cornell Cooperative Extension System and Implementation Plan- Year One, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    - Strategic Directions Implementation Plan-February 1998; Administrative Strategic Directions-2008-2012, 1998, 2008-2012 (Box 47, Folder 44A)
    - Teen Assessment Project Report, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 45)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Satellite Network and Distance Learning Task Group Report, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - GroNews - Consumer Horticulture, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Learning Well at Work, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 46)
    - Impact- Cornell University Addresses Contemporary Issues, 1997-1999 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - What's Cornell Cooperative Extension Doing in New York City?, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Survey of Rural Community Health Care Capacities and Structures, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - 4-H Youth Development Program-4-H Review Document, including the Report of the External Review Team, 1999-02-1999-03 (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - Communicating With Your Health Care Provider-New York City Programs (see also video), 2000 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Money 2000 Financial Fitness Workbook (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Week 2000 Documents (Box 47, Folder 47)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Week 2000 Documents (Box 47, Folder 48)
    - Emergency Preparedness Plan, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 49)
    - Impact- Cornell University Addresses Contemporary Issues, 2000-2001 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - New York State Residents Speak Out, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - Committing to Excellence, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - Agricultural Biotechnology: Informing the Dialogue by Shelton, 2002 (Box 53)
    - We Grow People - Profiles of Extension Educators, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Financial Security in Later Life, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Resource Notebook, 2004-01 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Money Works Project, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Grape Disease and Pest Identification Fact Sheet Set (Box 53)
    - Slug Identification Fact Sheet Set by K.S. Goh (Box 53)
    - Small Fruit Disease and Pest Identification Fact Sheet Set by Wilcox Wayne F (Box 53)
    - Tree Fruit Crops: Disease and Pest Identification Fact Sheet Set by Wilcox Wayne F (Box 53)
    - Vegetable Crops: Crucifer Disease and Pest Identification Fact Sheet Set (Box 53)
    - Potato Disease and Insect Identification Fact Sheet (Box 53)
    - Vegetable Crops: Cucurbits Disease and Pest Identification Fact Sheet Set (Box 53)
    - Snap Bean Pest Management by C H Petzoldt, 1998 (Box 53)
    - Strawberry IPM Scouting Procedures by J. Kovach, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Apple IPM by Agnello A, 1999 (Box 53)
    - Growing Alfalfa the IPM Way by J K Waldron, 1991 (Box 53)
    - IPM for Poinsettias in New York: A Scouting and Pest Management Guide by G Ferrentino, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Integrated Pest Management for Bedding Plants by Christine Casey, 2000 (Box 53)
    - Pest Flies of Pastured Cattle and Horses by Phillip E Kaufman, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Vegetable Crops: Onion Disease and Pest Identification Fact Sheet Set (Box 53)
    - Urban Pest Management: Strategies for Managing Pests in and around the Home by Carolyn Klass, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Urban Pest Management: Integrated Pest Management of Disease by Margery Daughtrey, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Seafood Savvy by Ken Gall, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Zebra Mussel: Impacts and Control by Charles R. O'Neill, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Aquatic Plants - Another World by David H. Greene, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Guidelines to Increase Survival of Released Sport Fish by Mark H. Malchoff, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Farmers Employment Workbook: Job Skills Development for Farmers by Debra Austic, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Farm Employee Wage Record Book, Agriculture Economics, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Cornell Farm Inventory and Depreciation Book, Agriculture Economics, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Economics of Apple Orchard Planting Systems by Gerald B White, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Rural Safety and Health: Lightning Protection for Farms by Diane Chamberlain, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Rural Safety and Health: Safer Farm Environment for Children by Ellen Abend, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Rural Safety and Health: Electrical Safety on the Farm by Diane Chamberlain, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Rural Safety and Health: Animal Handling Safety by Darcy Demmin, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Rural Safety and Health: Power Take-Off (PTO) Safety by Darcy Demmin, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Rural Safety and Health (Six Fact Sheet Set) by Eric Hallman, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Municipal Yard Waste Composting by Tom Richard, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Cornell Field Crops and Soils Handbook by G C Bergstrom, 1987 (Box 53)
    - Nitrogen and the Environment by M van Es Harold, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Cultivation Basics for Weed Control in Corn by Jane Mt. Pleasant, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Market Steer Record, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Astronomy: It's Out of This World (Leader/Member Guide) By Brian Rice, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Astronomy: It's Out of This World (Starchart) By Brian Rice, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Working With The Mass Media By Matthew Shulman, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Bait Hives for Honey Bees By Thomas D Seeley, 1989 (Box 53)
    - Gypsy Moth By Lawrence Abrahamson, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Insecticides for Gypsy Moth Control, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Small-Scale Queen Rearing by Beekeepers in the Northeast By Francis L W Ratnieks, 1988 (Box 53)
    - Beekeeping: General Information By R A Morse, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Integrated Pest Management for Onions By Michael Hoffmann, 1996 (Box 53)
    - The Selection, Care and Use of Plants in the Home By Charles C Fischer, 1986 (Box 53)
    - Rock Gardens By Jerry Stites, 1990 (Box 53)
    - Livable Landscape Design By John F Collins, 1988 (Box 53)
    - Athletic Field Maintenance: A Guide for Sports Turf Managers By Norman W Hummel Jr, 1988 (Box 53)
    - Pruning: An Illustrated Guide to Pruning Ornamental Trees and Shrubs (Older Edition) By Donald A Rakow, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Suggested Practices for Planting and Maintaining Trees and Shrubs (Older Edition) By Richard Weir, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Pressed Flower Pictures By Ann Hossenlopp, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Shrubs for Landscape Plantings in New York State By Robert G Mower, 1990 (Box 53)
    - Ornamental Grasses for the Home and Garden By Mary Hockenberry, 1997 (Box 53)
    - Gardening with Miniature Plants By Ernest F Schaufler, 1987 (Box 53)
    - Grow With the Flow: A Hydroponic Gardening Project By Philson A Warner, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Schefflera By Malcolm R Harrison, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Philodendron By James K Rathmell Jr (Box 53)
    - Home Lawns Varieties and Pest Control Guide By Mary C Thurn, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Cornell Home Grounds Guide for Ornamental Trees and Shrubs - Additional Notes, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Cornell Guide to Growing Fruit at Home By Marcia Eames-Sheavly, 2003 (Box 53)
    - Predicting Harvest Date Windows for Apples By G D Blanpied, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Pollination and Fruit Set of Fruit Crops By Roger D Way, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Integrated Weed and Soil Management in Fruit Plantings By Ian A. Merwin, 1998 (Box 53)
    - Cover Crops for Vegetable Production in the Northeast By L J Stivers, 1999 (Box 53)
    - Home Vegetable Garden Record By Roger A Kline, 1999 (Box 53)
    - Vegetable Production Handbook edited by Susan Pohl, 1994 (Box 53)
    - Safe Food Processing: It's In Your Hands By Robert G Gravani, 1984 (Box 53)
    - Managing Nuisance Beavers Along Roadsides By Paul G Jensen, 1999 (Box 53)
    - Reducing Deer Damage to Home Gardens and Landscape Plantings By Paul D Curtis (Box 53)
    - Home-Grounds-Garden: Resistance of Woody Ornamental Plants to Deer Damage By M J Fargione, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Production of Maple Sirup and Other Maple Products By F E Winch Jr, 1978 (Box 53)
    - Fish Management in New York Ponds By A W Eipper, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Birds of Prey: Understanding Predation and Northeastern Birds of Prey By Richard E Bonney Jr, 1981 (Box 53)
    - Timber Management for Small Woodlands By Gary R Goff, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Enhancement of Wildlife Habitat on Private Lands By Daniel J Decker, 1998 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife and Timber From Private Lands: A Landowner's Guide to Planning By Daniel J Decker, 1990 (Box 53)
    - Managing Small Woodlands for Firewood By Debbie M Van Ryn, 1987 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Notebook: Sketches of Selected Wildlife in New York State By Daniel J Decker, 1988 (Box 53)
    - Managing Canada Geese in Urban Environments: A Technical Guide By Arthur E Smith, 2000 (Box 53)
    - Know Your Trees By J A Cope, 2002 (Box 53)
    - Pond and Stream Safari: Activity Packet By Karen Edelstein, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Firewood: From Woodlot to Woodpile By Wanda Richberger, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Let's Go Ice Fishing By Ronald A Howard, 1989, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Water Worlds: Activity Packet By Janet E Hawkes, 1988 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Discovery: Activity Packet By Beth Silverman, 1989 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife in Today's Landscapes By Marianne E Krasny, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Basic Fly Tying By Ronald A Howard, 1990 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Bats By Paul D Curtis, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Moles By Kristi L Sullivan, 2002 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Crows By Kristi L Sullivan, 2002 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Reducing Deer-Vehicle Crashes By Paul Curtis, 2005 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Black Bear By Paul Curtis, 2005 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Racoons By Paul D Curtis, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Tree Squirrels By Paul D Curtis, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: White-Tailed Deer By Paul D Curtis, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Woodchucks By Paul D Curtis, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Snakes By Kristi L Sullivan, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Striped Skunks By Kristi L Sullivan, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Woodpeckers By Kristi L Sullivan, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management Fact Sheet: Voles By Kristi L Sullivan, 2002 (Box 53)
    - Wildlife Damage Management (13 Fact Sheet Set), Natural Resources, 2002 (Box 53)
    - Water Wise: Lessons in Water Resources By Elizabeth C Moran, 1989 (Box 53)
    - Know Your Tree Diseases By Juliet E Carroll, 1988 (Box 53)
    - Know Your Plant's Disease By Juliet E Carroll, 1987 (Box 53)
    - Mushrooms: To Eat or Not to Eat By Stanley Jay Smith, 1979 (Box 53)
    - Conifers: Spruce Gall Adelgids By George W Hudler, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Conifers: Needle Diseases of Scots Pine By George W Hudler, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Conifers: Needle Casts of Douglas Fir By George W Hudler, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Conifer Disease Identification (3 Fact Sheet Set) By George W Hudler, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Minor Fruits in New York State By Donald K Ourecky, 1980 (Box 53)
    - Top-Working and Bridge-Grafting Fruit Trees By G H Oberly, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Asparagus By R FSansted, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Cooperative Watershed Protection - What Makes it Work? By Lyle S Raymond Jr, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Composting: Wastes to Resources By Jean F Bonhotal, 1994 (Box 53)
    - What is Groundwater By Lyle S Raymond Jr, 1999 (Box 53)
    - Watershed Management: A Policy-Making Primer By Lyle S Raymond Jr, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Septic Systems, Soils and Groundwater Protection By Dennis P Swaney, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Watershed Conflict Resolution: Some Guiding Principles By Lyle S Raymond Jr (Box 53)
    - Common Wildflowers of the Northeast By Patricia Ellison, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Prevention of Youth Violence By Heidi Haugen (Box 53)
    - Project Ease: Leader's Guide By Karl Pillemer, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Project Ease: Member's Guide By Karl Pillemer, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Empowerment and Family Support (defective binding) By Mon Cochran, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Children and Divorce By Suzanne West, 1983 (Box 53)
    - Parent-Adolescent Communication By Florence Cherry, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Parenting: The Second Time Around By Jennifer Birckmayer, 2001 (Box 53)
    - The Know How Catalog (list of publications printed by Cornell's Colleges of Human Ecology and Agriculture and Life Sciences), 1976 (Box 53)
    - Parenting Skills Workshop Series: A Manual for Parent Educators By John Bailey, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Financial Fitness: Shape Up Your Spending By Jeanne M Hogarth, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Financial Fitness: Shape Up Your Spending (Spanish) By Jeanne M Hogarth, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Financial Fitness: Trim Your Credit Line By Jeanne M Hogarth, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Financial Fitness: Trim Your Credit Line (Spanish) By Jeanne M Hogarth, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Financial Fitness: Build Your Savings By Jeanne M Hogarth, 1986, 1994 (Box 53)
    - Financial Fitness: Build Your Savings (English and Spanish) By Jeanne M Hogarth, 1986, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Financial Fitness: Shape Up Your Spending By Jeanne M Hogarth, 1986 (Box 53)
    - Paycheck Planning:Nine Steps to Better Spending By Elizabeth Wiegand, 1981 (Box 53)
    - Family Health: Consumers in the Marketplace Picture Series By Lois Wright Morton, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Household Work: What's It Worth and Why? By W. Keith Bryant, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Financial Fitness for Young Adults By Barbara Bristow, 1998 (Box 53)
    - Public Hearings: A Guide to Effective Participation By Alan J. Hahn, 1980 (Box 53)
    - Promoting Women's Health: Across the Generations By Andrea Parrot (Box 53)
    - Talking With Kids About AIDS: Teaching Guide By Jennifer Tiffany, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Facility Planning and Management Notes (11 Fact Sheet Set) By Lorraine Maxwell, 2000 (Box 53)
    - Stenciling Chairs By Florence E Wright, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Providing Safe Drinking Water: A Primer, Textiles and Apparel, 2003 (Box 53)
    - Water Treatment Notes (14 Fact Sheet Set), Textiles and Apparel, 2004 (Box 53)
    - Am I a Good Role Model? By Winna Rivera, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Am I a Good Role Model? (Spanish) By Winna Rivera, 1997 (Box 53)
    - Calcium: It's Important, Nutritional Sciences, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Calcium: It's Important (Spanish), Nutritional Sciences, 2002 (Box 53)
    - Carbohydrates Building Blocks By Cynthia Bartok, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Carbohydrates Building Blocks (Spanish) By Cynthia Bartok, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Food for Health: Revitalize Your Recipies for Better Health (Pack of 25) By Christina Stark, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Energy: Everybody Needs It By Christianne Rich, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Energy: Everybody Needs It (Spanish) By Christianne Rich, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Fat: What Do You Need To Know? (Spanish) By Lisa Hilbert, 1990 (Box 53)
    - How Much Is A Serving? (25 pack) By Shauna Thomas, 2000 (Box 53)
    - How Much Is A Serving? (Spanish) (25 pack)By Shauna Thomas, 1997 (Box 53)
    - Iron: Who Needs It? By Josephine Connolly, 1989 (Box 53)
    - Iron: Who Needs It? (Spanish) By Josephine Connolly, 1990 (Box 53)
    - Northeast Regional Food Guide (Food List flyer) (25 pack), Nutritional Sciences, 2002 (Box 53)
    - Protein: A Nutrient That's Easy to Get By Christine Kaefer (Box 53)
    - Protein: A Nutrient That's Easy to Get (Spanish) By Christine Kaefer, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Taking Care of Two: Nutrition for Moms and Babies, 1990 (Box 53)
    - Taking Care of Two Educator's Guide By Tracy J Farrell, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Vitamin A: How To Get It By Arianna M Stupp, 2000 (Box 53)
    - Vitamin A: How To Get It (Spanish) By Arianna M Stupp, 2000 (Box 53)
    - Vitamin C By Winna T Rivera, 1994 (Box 53)
    - Vitamin C (Spanish) By Winna T Rivera, 2002 (Box 53)
    - Biology and Management of Apple Arthropods By Arthur M Agnello, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Bean Disease Identification (3 Fact Sheet Set), NYSAES, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Corn Disease and Pest Identification (10 Fact Sheet Set), NYSAES, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Tomato Disease and Pest Identification (7 Fact Sheet Set), NYSAES, 1987 (Box 53)
    - Pepper Disease and Pest Identification (3 Fact Sheet Set) By Thomas A Zitter, 1989 (Box 53)
    - Vegetable Fare: Displaying Vegetables at Their Best By Roger A Kline (Box 53)
    - Diversity: Evolving Language of Diversity By Kathy Castania (Box 53)
    - Diversity: What is Diversity By Kathy Castania (Box 53)
    - What's a Teacher to Do? Child Abuse Education for the Classroom By Lorrie Wolverton, 1987 (Box 53)
    - Horse Health Hints By N. Bruce Haynes, 1974 (Box 53)
    - Modern Agriculture: Its Effects on the Environment By Nancy M Trautmann, 1989 (Box 53)
    - Farm Families: Living and Working Together By Debra Austic, 1994 (Box 53)
    - Farm Family Letters: Letter # 8 By Virginia G Houseknecht (Box 53)
    - Home Fruit Planting By M B Hoffman, 1970 (Box 53)
    - Public Speaking Made Easy By Ortiz Darlene, 1991 (Box 54)
    - Cornell Recommendation Record Book, 2000 (Box 54)
    - Cornell Classic Farm Account Book By Wayne A Knoblauch, 2005 (Box 54)
    - Do You Know Your Valuable Papers? By ElizabethWiegand, 1989 (Box 54)
    - Home Composting (Packs of 25), Agricultural Biotech, 2003 (Box 54)
    - Milk Production Records For Management Control By Stanley Telega, 1997 (Box 54)
    - Positive Attitudes and Youth Horse Programs (25 pack) By Jean T Griffiths, 2001 (Box 54)
    - Astronomy: It's Out of This World (Complete - Guide + Chart) By Brian Rice, 1995 (Box 54)
    - Project LEAP: Grade 1 By Ruth Yarrow, 1995 (Box 54)
    - Project LEAP: Grade 2 By Ruth Yarrow, 1995 (Box 54)
    - Project LEAP: Grade 3 By Ruth Yarrow, 1996 (Box 54)
    - Project LEAP: Kindergarten By Ruth Yarrow, 1995 (Box 54)
    - Know Your Insects: Member's Guide By Carolyn Klass, 1981 (Box 54)
    - Home Lawns Establishment and Maintenance By Mary C Thurn, 1994 (Box 54)
    - Sequence of Bloom of Perennials, Biennials and Bulbs By Robert G Mower, 2003 (Box 54)
    - Pruning: An Illustrated Guide to Pruning Ornamental Trees and Shrubs By Donald A Rakow, 2005 (Box 54)
    - The Cornell Guide for Planting and Maintaining Trees and Shrubs By Richard Weir, 2005 (Box 54)
    - 2001-2003 Turfgrass Species and Variety Guidelines for New York State By Frank S Rossi (Box 54)
    - Lawn Care without Pesticides By Frank Rossi, 2005 (Box 54)
    - Using Plants to Bridge the Generations: Horticulture and Intergenerational Learning as Therapy By Vincent A Lalli, 1998 (Box 54)
    - Garden in the City By Mary Cockram, 1991 (Box 54)
    - Gardens of Fabulous Flowers By Donald A Rakow, 1992 (Box 54)
    - Orchard Nutrition Management By Warren C Stiles, 1991 (Box 54)
    - The Three Sisters: Exploring an Iroquois Garden By Marcia Eames-Sheavly, 2000 (Box 54)
    - The Great American Peanut By Marcia Eames-Sheavly, 1994 (Box 54)
    - The Humble Potato: Underground Gold By Marcia Eames-Sheavly, 1995 (Box 54)
    - Rice: Grain of the Ancients By Marcia Eames-Sheavly, 1996 (Box 54)
    - The Appealing Apple By Marcia Eames-Sheavly, 2000 (Box 54)
    - Homemade Wine By Willard B Robinson, 1982 (Box 54)
    - Insects All Around Us By Marianne E Krasny, 1992 (Box 54)
    - Diseases of Geraniums By R Kenneth Horst, 1985 (Box 54)
    - Detection of Potato Tuber Diseases and Defects By Thomas A Zitter, 1986 (Box 54)
    - Biological Control of Turfgrass Diseases By Eric B Nelson, 1992 (Box 54)
    - Dayneutral Strawberry Production Guide By Marvin P Pritts, 1989 (Box 54)
    - Cultural Practices for Commercial Vineyards By T D Jordan, 1980 (Box 54)
    - The Home Vegetable Garden By Leonard D Topoleski, 1981 (Box 54)
    - The Heirloom Vegetable Garden By Roger A Kline, 1981 (Box 54)
    - Weed Control For The Home Vegetable Garden By Robin R Bellinder, 1989 (Box 54)
    - The Garden Strawberry, 1982 (Box 54)
    - Your Septic System By A Meyer (Box 54)
    - Aquifers By Lyle S Raymond Jr, 2002 (Box 54)
    - Tug Hill Aquifer: A Guide for Decision Making By Mary Jane Porter, 1994 (Box 54)
    - Common Poisonous Plants, 1994 (Box 54)
    - Giant Hogweed, 1996 (Box 54)
    - Discipline is Not A Dirty Word, 2001 (Box 54)
    - Bookstart: Selected Activities for Babies to Young Children, 1996 (Box 54)
    - Teens as Parents of Babies and Toddlers: A Resource Guide for Educators, 1997 (Box 54)
    - Public Policy Education, 1993 (Box 54)
    - Rush Seats for Chairs, 1996 (Box 54)
    - In Support of Mobility: Kitchen Design for Independent Older Adults, 1992 (Box 54)
    - Adventures in Clothing Workbook, 1988 (Box 54)
    - Challenges in Clothing Workbook, 1998 (Box 54)
    - Strategies in Clothing Workbook, 1998 (Box 54)
    - Clothing Connections, 1982 (Box 54)
    - Removing Stains at Home, 2003 (Box 54)
    - In The Bag!: Families Sharing Science Together, 1995 (Box 54)
    - Kitchen Science for Kids, 2000 (Box 54)
    - Cooking Up Fun! A Pyramid of Snacks, 1998 (Box 54)
    - Cooking Up Fun! Muffins and More, 1999 (Box 54)
    - Cooking Up Fun! Yeast Breads, 2000 (Box 54)
    - Wine and Juice Grape Varieties for Cool Climates, 1993 (Box 54)
    - The Cornell Connection: A Historical Perspective (50 pack), 1991 (Box 54)
    - Catalog of Publications and Audiovisuals - 1994 (Box 54)